Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen, the morning chimes have arrived, and it's us, the Chiryu ABCs.
Before we begin, we'd like to choose today's MC.
Please vote for your favorite one or two. Whoever has the number card with that number on it is the MC.
Let's start voting!
Put your sleeves on!
What is this?
I wonder what it is.
Is it a rabbit?
It looks like a Sanrio character, but it's definitely not.
Oh, it's not?
Because it's pink.
Yes, it is pink.
That's why.
So cute.
And now, until the poll closes, five, four, three, two, one,
No.
Which one is bigger? It's not big.
Is it more?
Oh, there's more 2s.
Then we don't know either.
Okay.
Ready.
Yes.
So, the MC is Yuno-san.
Thank goodness. My voice is a bit slurred today.
So I'll try my best to get Riko to turn it over to me, and I'll be the MC for today.
This is Yuno.
Hang in there, Yunopi.
Yes, I'm Yunopi. Okay, let's begin.
Let's begin.
Okay.
Ebichu's...
Hilarious and ho-hum showroom.
Yay.
Oh no. My voice is getting worse.
Oh, it's out.
Well then, thank you very much for watching the 71st Ebituaries' Delightful and Fufufu Showroom today.
Thank you very much.
Ebichu's Delightful Showroom is the sister show of our sister showroom, Uka's Showroom.
So here is the time to spread the word.
In order to get as many people as possible to watch this distribution, I'm going to make an announcement on the official X of Ebichu now, so please spread the word.
Yay!
That's great.
That's it, you know,
I feel like I'm MCing every time I come to the showroom.
Really?
I'm MCing every time I come to vote.
That's great.
They know what I'm talking about.
Well, I'm going to do something like this today.
It's called, "Hilarious and Marital Survey Talk.
Yay!
Before we do the talk, we will take a questionnaire to decide what we will talk about.
That is the questionnaire talk.
Then, I'll give you a talk theme.
Yes, talk theme.
The talk theme is definitely the voice, right?
Yes, like this.
Yes, it's like this. Okay, everyone have a quick look at it.
Now, let's start voting!
There's something a little strange here,
Nakayama.
Ohira Expedition.
I want to see it.
I don't mind.
It was fun. It was fun.
Lucky festival, Harutsukawa Tachigi Park, there is one more talk that I want to talk about.
I always did it without writing my name. I always did it without writing my name.
I see, without writing your name. I'm not allowed to do that.
So I thought it would be Nakayama to say.
Five minutes, four, three, two, one, done.
Finished.
Well, what was the number?
Number 5?
Number 5 was 26.9%?
I mean, even if they picked number 5 or 6, I'm still...
I'm getting a little nervous.
Number 5.
Why did you open it?
That's me.
I had it pierced.
Why did you do it?
Because I'm about to answer that question.
I already have an answer.
I've had them for two months since April, and I've always loved jewelry. I have a big collection of earrings.
I've always loved jewelry, and I've collected a lot of earrings.
Is that it? End of the line?
When you beat it.
I'm sorry, I just really like to show off my face.
What's wrong with you?
I like to wear hair rings, but I can't wear them at a concert.
That's right.
So I decided to get my ears pierced in April, and now that they've stabilized, I can wear a variety of piercings,
I still only have this one piercing, and although I opened it, I don't have the desire for it right now...
I don't really have the desire to collect piercings, and it's just too much of a hassle.
Why did you open it?
So why did you open it? I don't know.
I don't even know.
I don't know.
But why didn't he come suddenly? He said he wanted to collect rings.
Ah, yes, there was.
But that's not coming now, so this is the only ring I have.
But it's cute and mature.
But it doesn't go with the outfit.
When there's a delivery or something, I knew that the costume...
I'm only allowed to wear things that match the outfit, and I'm only allowed to wear accessories that I've prepared,
I just don't wear it at night now, and it gets blocked up.
So you have great regenerative power.
Yes.
That's why I open my right ear every morning.
You open it every day?
Yes, my right ear gets plugged up every day,
That's why I don't wear it for a few hours.
Does it hurt when you wear it to bed?
This one hurts, but I have one that I can wear all the time, but the part that stops it disappeared in Taiwan, and I was told to go buy it as soon as possible.
But it's really a hassle to go and buy it.
I thought I would be able to buy one soon.
So we talked about why we opened the door.
He said that the right side tends to be blocked.
Why? Is that possible?
Is that possible?
Is that so? You tend to be right-side up?
Yes, I do. The left side is perfectly fine, but it's the right side every morning.
You mean you have pain every morning? It doesn't hurt. But it's a little bit irritated.
I think it's blocked. You say that when you put it on? Yes, yes, yes. It's like a "whip".
Scary story. It was a scary story.
It was a story. Let's go to the next one. Then, please vote. Please vote for the one you'd like to hear.
Yes, I did.
You said it's your first time. Thank you very much.
I thought you would be afraid of a buti.
I used to be a butch.
Good evening.
You're right. I've never seen a pair of ricochet before. Retail.
That's for sure.
I think we're getting together.
Let's go until we're all set.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Yes, sir.
I wonder.
One, Taipei.
I knew you wanted to ask about Taipei.
Yes, how was Taipei?
Did you have any good food?
Taipei.
You ate Chinese food every day.
Well, it's Chinese, of course.
I don't know.
I went to a food stall, Yoichi.
I did.
What did you eat? Mangoes. How many did you eat? How many did you eat? I ate 5. Isn't that amazing?
You didn't eat any food, right? I didn't eat any food. I had mangoes for dinner.
But it was really good, because I had a cup of mangoes for 250 yen, the size of a mango sold for 2,500 yen in Tokyo.
So I ate it.
Don't keep saying that. What did you eat?
What did you eat? What did you eat?
Some kind of daisy pie? Some mysterious thing.
I had a mystery thing. It was delicious. It was that round thing that looked like a rice cake.
It was like a rice cake... round and crunchy... with a chewy filling.
It tasted like a pondering without the seasoning. Ingredient flavor? - Ingredient flavor.
It's a little sweet, a little bit sweet, a little bit slightly sweet, and you can choose what you want to put on it, powdered sugar, whatever you want.
Not peppered rice cakes. Mine is delicious.
No one could find it. When I came back from Japan, I saw a TV show about Taiwanese food and they showed pepper cakes.
He said it's what I wanted to eat.
I wonder... What's the most memorable thing about Taipei?
Oh, I think the name was something like potato balls.
Yuna's most memorable memory is Yuna.
We were all gathered in a room together after the Teagei event, and Yuna said that her phone was at a certain percentage of charge, but she couldn't see the charge anymore.
I couldn't see the percentage of charge at first, and I was in a hurry, but then it stopped working.
So to comfort me, there was a vending machine on top of it, and it was selling food.
There was a rice vending machine and we went to buy some, but neither of us had enough change to buy it
Mayama-san and O-chan were just passing by, so they went out of their way to buy it in a hurry, just like that, with their hair done after taking a bath
After that, Yu decided to buy it, and Yu put the money in the machine, but it was too difficult to operate.
When Mayama-san operated the machine, Winter came down without any problem, but when Yu operated the machine, Winter broke.
The machine broke, too, and Yu was so depressed.
It's amazing how many things break and then break again.
He cried so hard and said he didn't want to be a part of it.
He sent the picture to a group of 10 people.
He's so cute.
She had her mouth in reverse, and she was wearing one of those strawberry caps that you put on the top of your head, and it was so cute.
It was so cute.
It was so cute, and I saw the inside of it.
I can't show you the inside, but...
But Yuna said I could ride on it, so maybe someday in a few years.
I was so happy.
I had a lot of fun.
I enjoyed the fall raising.
I wrote about three wishes in one day.
I've already written so many wishes, I think they'll come true.
I'm going to tease my fans, though.
I know I'm talking about it in all kinds of places.
Everyone is wishing for you to be happy,
Something about yourself,
I wish for you to do well in your work,
One person wrote "I wish for everything to go well,
Everyone else's was up beautifully, but his was the only one that caught fire,
It got caught in a tree and burned,
I thought to myself, "Wow, I shouldn't have done that.
I love this story, don't you?
It's interesting.
It was a good story.
It was fun. Thank you very much.
Well, then, continue.
Continue.
Please vote for what you want to hear.
I wonder what it is.
Well, yes. Jump belongs.
Let me see.
That's so cute.
I'm sure Yuna won't let you ride her until she does.
I love her too much.
After that,
Nonoka tried to make me laugh,
She sang a song that was popular at the time.
Yuka couldn't laugh, so she sang,
Yuna couldn't laugh,
Yuka couldn't laugh, so she hit the futon.
Nonoka was doing her best.
Five, four, three, two, one until the polls closed.
Four, three, two, one.
Eight.
Six?
This is Mr. Nakayama.
This is Nakayama. Okay, Nakayama, let me tell you a story.
Last year, Nonoka and I wanted to go to a shaved ice store,
We tried last year, but there was already a line and we couldn't go,
This time, too, we happened to go there after work, and it just happened to be open.
I went there again after work this time, and it just happened to be open,
I ordered it and it was delicious.
Did you see the picture?
There were many kinds of shaved ice, like hojicha shaved ice, strawberry and pistachio,
There were many kinds, like hojicha shaved ice, strawberry and pistachio shaved ice, and so on,
It was so delicious,
The staff will order it for the next time, right?
I saw them at the photo shoot for the next event,
I became friends with Yuzuki Ichikawa of AmeFlash,
We had talked about going to Yuzuki's shaved ice shop,
So I sent her a picture of the shaved ice.
I told Yuzuki-chan that we should go there, and we met at the Lucky Fest,
Yuno and Yuzuki-chan are both Midokuma, so neither of us was able to have a single conversation,
That's what I'm talking about.
Yu-chan is the same way.
She finally made a friend.
They go and live together.
It was a story of peace.
I'm worried about Midokuma.
Because they both talk every couple of days.
That's certainly true of Yuu.
Simply the opposite.
I appreciate it because I can go without worrying.
Please put your pictures up again.
I will.
How many more are there?
The end.
I'll leave you with about two more.
Then, please vote for the ones you want to hear.
Please vote for the ones you would like to hear.
Riko, do you go to ice cream stores?
I don't go there.
I can't eat all of it.
That's true.
I'm too full.
I guess two people can't eat more than one bowl of ice cream, can they?
Just now, Yuno was talking about the delicious ponderings she had in Taipei, like the taste of the ingredients.
Now that comment is being broadcasted. Now?
I'm so behind.
But the midikuma story is also coming in right now.
There's a huge time difference depending on who's watching.
I'm probably the one who's stuck in Taipei talking about how delicious pepper cakes are.
The shaved ice at the store is too big.
I'm still talking about Taipei.
Comment.
Please do.
Thank you very much.
Okay, until the deadline.
Five, four, three, two, one.
We're back.
Okay.
Number seven?
Mm-hmm.
I wonder.
It means you both have a dog.
You have a dog.
I'd like to have them play with me from Dockland someday.
It's going to be difficult because it's hot this time of year, but when it gets cooler.
Yuno's mother and Doriko's mother are good friends, aren't they?
They go to Dreamland together.
We go together, have dinner together before the concert, and so on.
Her mother also wanted to go.
What kind of dog do you have?
A toy poodle.
A Malpoo.
That's great.
Even if I take her to the dog run, she doesn't play with him.
We're the same. It's the same.
So I wonder what's going to happen.
Dogs don't recognize themselves as dogs, right?
So, when I took them to the dog run when they were small, they were like, "What the hell are these guys? They were at the end of the line.
They don't even know they are dogs.
They don't even know they are dogs. They don't even know they are dogs.
So when you put them close to the mirror, their eyes don't meet yours? No, they don't.
You don't look at yourself? I don't think he thinks of me as a weatherman.
When you go for a walk, he barks at the big dogs, doesn't he? He goes to watch the fight.
It's amazing. They are not afraid. On the contrary, I heard that Chiba is afraid of them.
Chiba is strong, but he even goes up against huskies and such.
That's amazing.
He doesn't like dogs, but he likes women.
I understand.
When he walks normally and passes men, he walks normally, but when he passes a woman, he shrugs like this.
I think he is a boy.
On the other hand, the girls in my family are not very good with old ladies.
She is fine with young girls and grandmothers.
Really?
And I'm fine with grandfathers, grandpas, and men, too,
I just can't handle aunts and uncles.
I see.
If I bring my mother, she might bark at me.
But if she's nice, I'm sure she'll be fine.
She'd probably just say, "You're so cute.
Oh, it'll make it harder for me to get cancer.
She'd tell me not to touch her.
It really hurts.
Listening to Yuu's story, I can't help but miss Hayaki-chan.
You're great, Hayaki-chan.
We've become good friends. I wonder how it's going to be?
I'm looking forward to it.
Does he have a similar personality to his owner?
Yes, they are similar in the way they take care of things.
Maybe they are similar.
I've been told that our faces are starting to look alike.
Lately, people say I'm starting to look like Ukku.
I don't think it's the other way around.
I don't think it's always the opposite.
I've been told in various ways that I'm starting to look like Ukku.
Mr. Fujii told me, and the principal also told me.
Yes.
It's not the opposite? It's not the other way around.
That's for sure.
I was comparing it with the distribution.
I want an EBITCHU dog project.
I think it could be done on YouTube or something, a dock run.
I'm sure you can do it on YouTube or something.
My sisters' sisters,
On the contrary, you buy a lot of menga.
Except for Cocona, you bought a lot of menga.
Kao-chan, too,
Kao-chan also buys menga at grandma's house.
I don't think we'll ever be able to buy Cocona.
You said you wanted to buy it.
Cocona bought it at her grandma's house, didn't she?
Oh, oh, she said.
I want her to do it next week.
I want her to.
Yuna, Yunan family's J-kun is also coming from Fukuoka.
Hey.
It's like that.
Okay, then, I'll go last, too.
Last.
Shall we go?
Well, then, please vote.
I wonder, what will be chosen?
It's true that Mire is the only cat, though.
That's right.
I feel really good about number 3.
Certainly Cocona, that one, Doberman and Kasky, or something, seems to be winning.
It sure looks like they're winning.
So then, five, four, three, two, one until justice.
What is it?
Third.
Lucky Fest.
Yes, lucky festival.
Lucky Fest. It was hot outside.
But, you know, the weather held up.
Yes, it was. It was nice. It looked like it was raining to begin with.
Yes, yes, yes.
It was supposed to rain for three days.
But it cleared up.
It was only sunny for one day, right?
Yes, it did.
I'm very happy about that.
It was sunny. I'm so happy. The set was very summery,
Blue and blue star names from Nokuia wood, Labisma, etc... It was summer, wasn't it?
It was summer.
I didn't know they allowed people to take pictures. Yes, people were taking videos, and they were streaming on TikTok and other places.
Thank you very much. Summer festivals are fun, aren't they?
I don't know if it is yet,
It's been three years since I joined Ebimachi. So I'm not used to festivals like that,
Backstage at festivals, there are usually a lot of celebrities lined up in a row,
It was like a hut,
Hut?
One group at a time?
So when I went outside, I saw celebrities walking around.
So when I went outside, I felt like I was in the presence of celebrities.
And the food was delicious.
It was delicious.
The food at the festival. This time, we couldn't stay until the night because of the traffic jam, but we enjoyed the food after the concert and went home.
What was good?
Pizza! Oh, did you have Yu's pizza? There was a pizza with shrubs cheese,
I wonder if everyone at the festival got a chance to try it? What did you eat? Lucky festival, did you eat any festival food?
I was so happy when the candy corner was over.
We talked about Ki-chan.
The one about how they're closer than they are... it came on while we were talking.
I knew it. I'm a little behind.
Let's put it in the middle.
I wanted to eat candy ice cream.
Cocona was eating it during the broadcast.
Yes, she did, didn't she?
The ham skewers were delicious.
They were delicious.
I wonder what it was.
It was about Lulu Ohan and her precious pineapple.
It's complicated. Which one?
It looks like it could be.
It looks like it could be at Fesmeth.
It was delicious too.
There was also a Yakult corner,
They have a great ice cream place, and the Yakult line is like a bar.
I appreciated the corner next to the Yakult line.
There was a candy corner, wasn't there?
When I arrived at the venue, there were a lot of jellies before checking on the members.
Everyone is eating, but they are still eating sweets.
Yes. Jell-O, and also fugashi.
It's amazing, isn't it? Can't you even put pasta in your mouth anymore?
I'm not surprised. Fugashi is sweet.
Really?
Fugashi is delicious, isn't it?
It's delicious, isn't it?
The rule of Lucky Fest is a cup of dashi. Oh, I didn't know that.
And that was delicious too. What was it called again?
That, like a stamina donburi. What else?
Yuna said it was delicious.
And the Bean-curd soup with red pepper paste? It was delicious.
I don't think I ate it. The dipping sauce was delicious.
Last year, there was grilled ayu, and this year there wasn't, but I want to eat it again.
I hope I can come back year after year. I hope they are watching us.
Lucky Face.
I have one memory of Lucky Face.
When I arrived by car, the car receptionist was the first to say good morning, which was kind of funny at that point.
I was grateful for his energy, but he was the last one to leave, and he was the only one who went.
I thought, "Lucky festival is such a sense of tension.
It was fun.
The next festival will be in Gifu?
Yes, Gifu.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all there.
It looks hot.
August 6?
Six.
All wrong.
What's the date of formation? Sixth.
What?
Three days.
Maybe it's the 3rd.
Three days is totally different.
The formation date is the 4th.
It's all wrong.
Chiyo, what's the six? What's 6?
I don't know.
Split up with my sister.
I've decided for my sister.
I've decided.
That's great. I'm sorry.
Of course. I'm sorry.
It's after episode 6, but I'm ready.
But, the main block is really bumped up too, isn't it?
That's for sure.
Maybe I shouldn't say it's super interesting, but there are some elements that will make you feel like you're in a daze.
Please come visit us. I'll be waiting for you.
That's all for now.
Okay.
Next, here's the plan. A pleasant and windy July.
For the rest of the time, I would like to do some July-ish projects.
What are you going to do?
I don't know, but I think it would be fun to have a showdown of players who would spend 1,000 yen of their allowance at a summer festival on how many people they would spend it on.
Sure thing. Let's do it.
Let's do it.
Good morning.
I got 1,000 yen allowance at the summer festival.
The price tag is 50 yen.
What do you want to spend it on? I wonder what it's for.
I wonder.
But isn't this going to be that?
If there is an Uta village in Famien, it would be like a spoiler for it.
If there is.
Certainly.
That's right. What I want to eat.
Well, well, well.
There we go.
What do you think it is?
I don't know the price.
Do you go on trips around the globe?
When I lived in Aichi.
I did. You want to eat, right?
Food.
But only food?
What would you spend your allowance on? I don't know.
Anything.
Even dumplings.
Oh.
A candy apple.
What should it be?
How much is it?
Candy apples, 300 yen.
Oh, I shouldn't have said that.
Okay.
I wonder how much it is.
I wonder.
Summer festivals and such have started, right?
I want to wear a yukata.
It's so cute.
Let's see.
It's hardened.
I just spent 700 yen.
I just spent 500 yen.
Ehhhh...
So...
What do we have here?
100 yen more
Is that the same guy?
What can we do for 100 yen?
Can't we do yo-yos and stuff for 100 yen?
How much do you have?
200 yen, 300 yen, right?
100 yen
I don't know.
100 yen?
100 yen
I should have made it a good barrage.
Right?
100 yen
I wonder...
I could do a game or something for 100 yen.
See you tomorrow.
I wonder...
Thanks for watching, I'll see you in the video!
OK.
OK, OK.
Shall we make an announcement?
Okay, I'll start with Yuno.
Okay, I'll start with Yuu's.
Apple candy 300 yen, apricot candy 200 yen, yakisoba 400 yen, wanage 100 yen.
I forgot yakisoba.
All of you have something sweet.
Candy apples are a standard item, aren't they?
I had an apricot candy for the first time when I came to Tokyo.
You can't find it in Aichi Prefecture, so I ate it for the first time and it was delicious, so I had apricot candy.
I brought some yakisoba with rice, yakisoba for 400 yen, and a ring toss to get a yo-yo or something.
I put yakisoba in the ring.
Okay, Riko.
Pickled cucumber 200 yen, cotton candy 500 yen, ramune 200 yen, ring toss 100 yen.
I knew it was a ring toss.
That one is 100 yen.
I thought Watarame was surprisingly expensive. Indeed. The character.
I thought it would cost about 500 yen. That's for sure.
There are no noodles. I forgot about the ramen type. I've been eating ramen after I got home.
I had an image of a huge line for ramen restaurants. The last time I went there, there was a huge line and all they served was ramen and other small things.
That's for sure.
I happened to have a lesson at a festival in Ebisu when I was there, so I ate five apricot candies there.
Five?
That's amazing.
I found one, ate it, and brought two back home to eat.
This was a showdown between the players.
Voting.
Okay, 1 and 2.
Please vote this way.
I'm really not sure about this one.
I forgot the yakisoba.
But I can eat it at home.
At home?
Yes, I can.
Rittan says he never gets tired of cucumbers.
I never get tired of it.
It's a freebie.
Until the polls close.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Oh, wow.
Which one is it?
Oh, I was number two.
Well, it's about the same, isn't it?
That's for sure.
Well, that's about it,
What are you going to do next?
A Tanabata project.
Let's write our wishes and put them on the wall.
I have made many wishes in Taipei.
And there was a place to write them at the hotel, too.
I did it at the hotel, too.
The day I went there was the Tanabata festival.
Six, seven, eight.
I wonder what it is. Tanabata.
Well, I've already written four wishes here.
What did you write? At the raising of the star.
You wrote three wishes at the raising of the sun, right?
I wrote three wishes.
What did I write?
Good luck with the test.
What? I don't know.
I think people might be a little more upset with you.
Individually.
I remember the last time I wrote "lower grade members" and "upper grade members",
I don't remember the part before that.
I don't remember the one before that.
I don't know.
I'll do my best on SNS.
Borrowing cool stuff.
I haven't posted on TikTok since right after I went there.
So I'm glad that I borrowed the parentheses.
One more thing.
Riko.
I'm going to start with social networking,
And 100,000 followers on Instagram,
I forgot one more thing.
Don't lose your wallet.
Is that okay?
Yes.
You lost it?
I lost it on the first night,
I lost it.
That's right.
But I thought for sure I just put it in the wrong place, so when I came back to the hotel, I found it.
I don't lose things.
You don't lose things, do you?
You don't lose things.
What did you think, Riko?
What did you think of me? I can't remember the other one.
The 100,000 Instagram SSA success.
One more thing.
It's not everyone's wish.
Insta and..,
I wonder.
Well, but what I'm wishing for the most right now.
I did some research about 2 years ago,
I found out about 2 years ago that Tanabata means "May you do it several times," or "I'll do it several times.
Also, the address and so on.
I was told to write it down properly. It will be the address of the office.
I found that out about 2 years ago. I'll write down my Instagram and Twitter IDs so people will know me today.
Sure. I wonder what it is.
I'll start with my ID. What is my ID?
What is it called, fans, on my Instagram?
My username.
Please send me an official one.
I'm sure.
I'm on Instagram, Twitter, X, and TikTok.
I'll write them all down.
Wow.
All of them have the user's M value.
Rika Nakayama is official.
Just like that.
Okay, a wish.
What about the camera account?
Oh, that?
Down, down, down.
God ins check it.
I wonder what that is.
Thank you very much.
God all.
Then it's all in plain sight.
Insta.
X
Insta
It only says Insta.
Okay, okay.
I wonder what it is, I can't think of a little wish I wrote down.
I'm going to pretend I met with Mr. Tada of Tamo at the hotel and the Parliament.
You wrote two Tada of Tamos.
Right.
You wrote a total of five wishes.
Yes, I did.
I wonder...
May I ask you to come in here?
It was written somewhere.
Maybe vertical is the right answer.
Okay.
You're going to put this up somewhere in the studio.
Okay, then.
It's done.
I'll be a proper 18 year old.
So, various IDs.
Proper?
I'll be a proper 18.
Yes.
Now next March.
Just on SAC Day.
That's right.
That's great.
But until now, there have been no live concerts in March.
So I've never had anyone celebrate with me,
So we're celebrating with a spring tour production.
It's not fair.
I don't have a concert in October either.
That's for sure.
I will work.
I'll go back to my hotel strip and do my work.
Well, that's the most important thing.
Because, I will work a lot.
Yes, thank you for your work.
Where should I put it? Maybe on the Kumano head.
Is that okay? Let's put it on your left ear.
Put it on this side. Do you want to cover your face?
Just for a few minutes. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Just a few minutes. Okay. Okay.
All right. What's next?
What's next?
One more thing.
Oh, one more thing.
I don't know if this is going to happen, but do you want to think about our plans for the summer?
Oh, sure.
The ages.
Last year we went to the pool with Yuna,
Oh, that's right.
We're going again this year.
I was kind of black, blackened.
You were slightly tanned. No, no, I was burnt.
What, I want to go grunting or something. Oh, I want to.
I want to play in some kind of river. Um, I want to do that.
Nagashi Somen. Oh, I want to do that.
But there aren't many places where you can do Nagashi Somen. Yes, but I want to do it in Paglieri.
I don't know. I don't know, a cup yard or something.
I think we can do Nagashi Somen if it's done well. Sure.
To many. No, there aren't. I want to do Nagashi Somen.
I'm going to ask Cocona to drive, because she hasn't even gotten her driver's license yet, and I don't know if she'll be able to do it.
But I want to do fireworks, because we did it the night before rehearsal.
We had a successful fireworks display.
I want to deliver.
I wonder...
Yamada High School can't swim, right?
It depends on how you feel. But did you see that one? The one with the ducks. The famous one.
I hope they have a camp fan. They're going to have a "Song Men" party on August 8.
Enjoy it.
I don't know anything about it.
I wonder what Yuna and the others will do.
I wonder.
I want to have a barbecue.
Someday with 10 people.
They said that last year, so I'm sure they'll say it again next year.
I'm sure they'll say it next year, too.
Someday.
It would be nice if we could do it someday.
Yes, it would be nice.
It's just time, right?
It's just about time, so that's all for Yukari and a happy August.
Oh no.
It's over.
It was a Yukari-de-fu-fu July.
Crackle, crackle, crackle.
Yes, it's the 71st edition of the Emitude Yukari de Fuwufuna Showroom, and it's coming to an end in the blink of an eye.
Now, let's hear RICO's announcement.
RICO's?
Mine.
Maybe over there.
Oh, no, no.
Yes.
Can I use cucumbers or something?
It's all cucumbers.
Cucumbers.
Oh, here it is.
First of all, the announcement of Ebichu. To the families of Ebichu Summer.
It will be held at Yamanakako Koryu Plaza Kirara Theater Hibiki on August 17 and 18, 2024.
Please ask for our help.
Osetori and costumes.
The costumes are cute, aren't they?
They are cute, aren't they?
We are making progress little by little, so please look forward to it.
Please come visit us for sure.
We'll be waiting for you.
And yesterday, we made an announcement.
Kahoriko's 10th anniversary live, Kahoriko in Solmi.
It has been 10 years since his marriage and tendon.
The event will be held on September 14, 2024.
Saturday, September 14, 2024.
It will be held at J.COM HALL Hachioji.
This is,
This too,
Please come for sure.
By the way, please come to the next one, too.
Please come to this one, too.
Yes.
Next one,
Huh?
I skipped one.
Oops.
Riko Nakayama's Birthday Solo Live, the Birthday Festival of Riko Nakayama will be held at ZEPP Shinjuku on Tuesday, October 29, 2024.
Please come to this one, too, for sure.
Please everyone come to all of the emichun's schedule.
If you don't come, it's going to be open to the public later on. Both the Kamen and the Kamoriko live performance.
Hot.
Please let me win the ticket. We don't even know if there will be a distribution,
Please come anyway. I don't think there was one last year, so please come to my birthday party.
I'll be there.
Here it is, the final ranking. It's been too long since I've done this, but there it is.
Fifth place! No. 4?
It's from K-BUN. Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Jimmy. Thank you very much.
Third place, Enzu-san. Thank you very much. Second place, Clone 12.
Thank you very much.
First place, Koyuki, it's your birthday.
Strong birthday tone. Congratulations.
Congratulations, and thank you very much.
How was it? It was a very loose delivery, wasn't it?
It was a very loose delivery.
How did you like it?
No?
A radio letter?
First time I've seen it. Thank you very much.
We will finish in a few minutes.
See you next month.
Who's coming?
Are you thinking of having a talk with them?
Me?
Yes, I am.
I'm not thinking about the birthday party,
I haven't thought about Kaboriko's birthday yet, but I've already decided on Kaboriko's.
Then, if I say I still want to sing this song at Riko's birthday party,
Is there any possibility?
It's totally possible.
On the contrary, please do.
If there is a song you would like me to sing, please do so.
Explain slingshots.
Sure, sure.
We were running out of songs without any sense of discomfort.
We didn't know what it was, but we saw it at the entrance,
So we put it on.
Riko said, "This is for you," so I said, "This is for Yuu.
We were now matching.
It was definitely time for a photo shoot.
Are my eyes too far apart? I can't tell your eyes at all.
Maybe it's the other way around. Maybe it's what I'm saying.
I can't get a good shot.
That's cute too.
What do you think? Did you get it?
Thank you for the 3 days of the live.
Thank you all for the three days.
This is the end of the 71st edition of Ebitu's Delightful and Unpleasant Showroom.
We will let you know about the next delivery as soon as it is decided.
That's all for now.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for watching.